

# Sriparna Sinha

I am looking for Angular Developer position that provides me opportunities where I can make the best of my potential in a challenging environment and contribute to the development of the organization. Having 2.3years of experience in Govt (Contractual). I had completed MCA and I love to learn new things and explore in different areas.

# Asansol. India. 713305

+918348649438

⊕ 09/01/1992

HTML

JavaScript

Angular

Word

Java

sri.parna192@gmail.com

CSS

**TECHNICAL SKILLS** 

**TypeScript** 

**RDBMS** 

Bootstrap

MongoDB (NoSQL)

PowerPoint

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **INOCENTUM TECHNOLOGIES, IT COMPANY**

Webel IT Park, Asansol

01/06/2022- Present

Inocentum Technologies is a professionally managed software development and consulting house. Achievements/Tasks

- At present working as a Trainee.
- Working on CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Angular, Bootstrap.
- MongoDB basic queries (NoSQL DBMS)
- Creating my portfolio website using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript in Angular framework. Basically, creating static Angular websites and used how to move one module to another in Angular and upload in <a href="https://github.com/Sriparna192/">https://github.com/Sriparna192/</a>

# PASCHIM BANGA SOCIETY FOR SKILL DEVELOPMENT (PBSSD) Utkarsh Bangla, Project Assistant cum DEO (PADEO) (Contract)

District Magistrate Office, Asansol

03/02/2020 - 31/05/2022

- I was part of the team on State Govt. Project Utkarsh Bangla, PADEO as Contractual basis.
- Under this scheme there are many training centres and giving skills to youths under Industries
  who are from rural/urban area.
- Monitoring all the centres and Industries. Handling weekly meetings with Hons. DM, ADM (skills), and the team of Utkarsh Bangla.
- There's a portal pbssd.gov.in, maintaining and upgrading day by day. All works related to this field maintaining by computer system and have to survey field/Industries.
- Working with Word, Excel, PowerPoint. Different types of Data Entry work in this field.
- Maintaining Accounts/ Cashbook.

### KALLA HARIPADA HIGH SCHOOL

Kalla, Asansol

**Computer Teacher (Contract)** 

05/03/2018 - 15/07/2019

 Teaches the Basic Computer, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Digital Logic, C Programming Language, Networking (Basic)

## **EDUCATION QUALIFICATION**

#### **MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION (MCA)**

Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Technology, University of Kolkata

**Institute:** Asansol Engineering College (2014-2017)

CGPA: 8.81

#### **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION**

**University of Burdwan** 

**Institute:** Asansol Girls' College (2011-2014)

Percentage: 73.74%

HIGHER SECONDARY (SCIENCE), W.B.C.H.S.E

Institute: Asansol Girls' School (2011)

Percentage: 59.60%

SECONDARY, W.B.B.S.E

Institute: Burnpur Girls' High School (2008)

Percentage: 70.62%

## **HOBBIES/INTEREST**

Painting, Chess, Programming, Playing with musical instruments

# PROJECTS/ TRAINING

Excel

MCA Major Project on 'TOUR & TRAVEL'. Software uses Android SDK, IDE: Eclipse, DB: SQLITE. [The main objective of this android application to provide best travelling services that user can search places and booking bus, flights.]

MCA Minor Project on 'E-LEARNING'. Software uses ASP.NET, C#, DB: SQL Server. [The main objective of this project to share skills and knowledge through web based.]

#### **Academic Achievements**

Training on **ASP.NET** on Sep 2013 to Jan 2014 as N.K. Technology Institute.

Attended workshop on "ESSENTIAL OF DIGITAL SAFETY & SECURITY" & "LINUX & ANDROID" at Asansol Engineering College.

#### **LANGUAGES**

### Bangla

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **English**

Professional Working Proficiency

Hindi